alaplaya.net 2015-12-28

# Play the Best MMO, Browser, and Mobile Games for Free

## Privacy Policy

Aeria Games GmbH is committed to protecting your privacy and creating a strong relationship with our users. This privacy policy explains the use of personal information collected via (i) our websites, whether at www.aeriagames.com or other uniform resource locators (URLs) owned or operated by us, and (ii) our products and services, including without limitation those that we provide via our websites, other third party platforms, and desktop and mobile applications (collectively, all of the foregoing in clauses (i) and (ii) are referred to as our "Services"). 

This policy does not apply to (a) the practices of companies that we do not own or control, (b) people that we do not employ or manage, (c) third party websites, whether linked to or from our Services, (d) information that you provide to us for purposes of seeking employment, provision of services to us, business proposals or similar matters, (e) information that you provide to us unsolicited, or (f) information that we collect offline.

As used in this Privacy Policy, "personal information" means information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, e-mail address, phone number or physical address.

###  Important: If you do not agree with any terms or conditions described in this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Services.

### Information That We Collect

We may collect different information from you when you use our Services. The following are examples to help you better understand the types of information that we collect. 

1\. Information That You Provide Directly

When you use our Services, we may collect information that you provide to us directly, including without limitation:

_Registration and Profile Information._ Your username, password, and other related information for purposes of registration or creating a profile.

_Payment Information._ Your credit card numbers and other billing information for completing transactions.

_Publicly Shared Information._ Information that you share publicly via our Services, such as postings in community forums, message boards and blogs, chat in public channels, and your public profile. (Please be aware that such information is public information. You should not expect privacy or confidentiality under these circumstances, and we shall not be liable in any way for disclosure of such information.)

_Information for Customer Support._ Information that you provide when you contact us for assistance or to report a problem.

_Friends List._ Your friends list (e.g. if you refer others to our Services or form a group within our Services).

_Sweepstakes/Promotions._ Information that you provide in order to participate in sweepstakes and promotions.

2\. Information Collected Through Technology

We collect information through technology to make our Services more useful and interesting to our users, including without limitation:

_Cookies._ We may use cookies to track general, non-personal information about our users for statistical and market research purposes (e.g., user name, pages viewed, time spent on applications, websites visited just before and just after our Services, etc.). This information is collected on an aggregated and anonymous basis.

_Log Files._ Like most Internet services, we may also use log files on the server side. The data held in log files includes your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit websites, device type, date/time stamp, and user activity (e.g., feature usage, user rankings, game statistics).

_Temporary Files._ In addition, the software enabling our websites may have associated log and temporary files that are stored on our servers. These files store your account information, preference settings, system notifications as well as other data necessary to enable you to use our Services. Your information may also exist within regularly performed server backups. This information is collected on an aggregated and anonymous basis. 

_Patches._ When any game or application is updated or "patched," our patch routine may check your device to see that you have the most recent version of the files.

On an aggregated and anonymous basis, we may also collect other information through technology, such as information on our users' hardware, operating systems, and usage patterns.

3\. Information Received Through Your Third Party Platform Account and Mobile Device

When you use or connect to our Services on or through a third party platform, such as a social networking site (including using a third party platform account to sign into our Services), you allow us to access and/or collect certain information from your third party platform profile/account as permitted by the terms of the agreement and your privacy settings with the third party platform. The information you allow us to access and collect varies, depending on the Service you use, the terms of the third party platform and your privacy setting there. You may be able to disallow the third party platform from providing us with certain information about you by changing your privacy settings there.

If you use a our Services via a mobile device, we may, in accordance with the terms of any applicable agreement with the mobile device carrier (and as allowed by your privacy settings) collect certain information such as your unique device identifier (a number automatically assigned to your mobile or wireless device), device type, and information you choose to provide or share, such as e-mail address.

### How We Use Your Information

We may use the information we collect for a variety of purposes, primarily for operating and improving our Services. Our uses include without limitation:

_Communications._ Communications with you about your account and our Services, such as new features and offerings.

_Services._ Providing our Services, such as fulfilling requests and resolving customer support issues.

_Analysis._ Analyzing trends and user behavior to improve our Services and develop new Services.

_Protection._ Protecting our Services from misuse and, as may be necessary or appropriate in our determination, to protect the safety and security of our users, employees and third parties, or the integrity of our Services.

Among other forms of communications, we may send push notifications to your mobile device to provide game updates and other relevant messages. You can manage push notifications from the "options" or "settings" page within the mobile application. You also may be able to manage them from your device's settings page. 

Finally, we may take your personal information and make it non-personally identifiable. We do this either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating your information with information about other individuals), or by removing characteristics (e.g., your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. This process is known as de-personalizing your information. Given the non-personal nature of this information, no restrictions apply under this Privacy Policy on our right to use de-personalized information.

### Sharing of Information with Third Parties

We will not share your personal information with unrelated third party advertisers.

We will only share your personal information with third parties under the following circumstances:

_Our Service Providers._ We may utilize or partner with other companies to provide our Services, such as vendors and service providers that analyze customers' interaction with our Services, and handle consumer surveys, or companies that co-develop or co-publish games with us. While providing their services, these companies may access your personal information, but we will direct them to maintain the confidentiality of such information and use it solely for performing the applicable services. 

_Required Disclosures._ We will disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that disclosure is required or permitted by law (e.g., court order or subpoena) or such disclosure helps (i) enforce our terms of use, contests, sweepstakes, promotions, game rules, or similar restrictions, or (ii) protect the safety and security of our users, employees and third parties, or the integrity of our Services. 

_Mergers and Corporate Transactions._ In the event that we undergo a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, joint venture, corporate divestiture or dissolution, a sale of assets, or similar transactions, we may share, disclose or transfer your information, including personal information, to the other organizations that are parties to such transactions. 

_Sweepstakes and Promotions._ We may share your information in connection with any sweepstakes or promotions you enter in connection with our Services, as necessary to administer, market, sponsor, administer or fulfill them or as required by applicable laws, rules or regulations.

_Offers._ Our Services may display "offers" that are hosted by third party providers. The offers may, for example, provide virtual currency to users in exchange for interacting with an advertisement or for completing a marketing offer. To properly credit user accounts and to prevent fraud, a unique identifier, in some cases your user ID, may be shared with the offer providers. Please be aware that, after clicking on one of these offers, you will no longer be on our Services, and information that you provide will go directly to the third party provider. 

_With Your Permission._ Additionally, if you opt-in or otherwise agree to have your information shared with a third party (or third parties), we will share your information accordingly, in which case the third party's use of your information is subject to the third party's own privacy policy.

As discussed above, we may use de-personalized information in any way, including sharing it with third parties, without your consent. Among other things, we may share some of the information we collect from you upon installing a mobile application with vendors and other service providers who are working with us in connection with the operation of Our Services and/or for analytics purposes which may require the reproduction and display of de-personalized information. You may be able to "opt out" of the collection of your information for third party analytics purposes by following the directions provided by our third party analytics vendor. If you "opt out" with one third party analytics provider, that action is specific to that provider only and does not otherwise limit our information collection under the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

### Security of Your Information

We are committed to safeguarding your information, and we implement reasonable security measures to protect the security of your information. We also constantly update our technology with the goal of better protecting your information. 

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will not occur. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe, to use strong passwords, to log out of your account after use, and to use different passwords for different services with different companies. It is important that you also help protect and maintain the security of your account. Please notify us immediately of any unauthorized use. 

### Age Requirement

We will not knowingly collect, use or retain personal information from anyone under the age of 13, for any purpose whatsoever (including internal or external marketing or promotional purposes). If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us. 

### Modification of Privacy Policy

We may periodically update and modify our privacy policy to reflect changes in the types of information we collect, the means we use to collect information, and/or our usage of collected information. We will attempt to notify you of any such update or modification. However, you are responsible for periodically reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site and/or any products or services offered by Site signifies your assent to the updated or modified Privacy Policy. 

### Right to Access

Users in certain jurisdictions have a right to access personal information held about themselves. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with applicable law. Please submit any requests for access to your personal data in writing to [privacy@aeriagames.com](mailto:privacy@aeriagames.com)

### Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please send an e-mail to [privacy@aeriagames.com](mailto:privacy@aeriagames.com)
